Contact

41984935138 (Mobile) ferreirasara1501@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ ferreirasara1501 (LinkedIn) github.com/ferreirasara (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Test Automation Manual Testing Vue.js

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Português (Native or Bilingual)

Sara Ferreira

Frontend Developer | React.js | Typescript | Javascript Campo Largo, Paraná, Brazil

Summary

Sara got interested in computing when as a child. Graduated in Computer Science and have been working with development for more than four years. On whatever project Sara works on, automated testing and comprehensive code are priorities. Sara has experience at both frontend and backend but prefers to work with frontend, ideally in a remote role.

Experience

FireFly.Bot
Full Stack Developer
May 2023 - Present (8 months)
Curitiba, Paraná, Brasil

- Integration with CRM systems.
- Development of backend GraphQL queries and mutations.
- Database integration with Prisma ORM.
- CRUD development using React.
- Utilization of React Hooks with GraphQL queries and mutations.
- Performance improvements of Web pages by optimization of GraphQL queries.
- Development of chatbot conversation flows.
- Created Jest test cases.
- Utilization of TypeScript at both frontend and backend.
- Pagination and sorting on queries
- Importing and normalizing data from real estate databases
- Remote worker.

Miggos (YC W22) Frontend Developer November 2022 - April 2023 (6 months) São Paulo. Brasil

- Creation of new Vue components using Figma mockups.
- Use of Storefront UI components.
- Use of CSS to customize Storefront UI components.

Page 1 of 3

- Use of GIT for version control.
- Use of Nuxt.js
- Use of TypeScript.
- Agile development.
- Remote work.

Livus

Frontend Engineer

June 2022 - November 2022 (6 months)

São Paulo, Brasil

- Creation of new React components using Figma mockups.
- Created unit test cases using Jest.
- Created integration tests cases using Cypress.
- Utilization of Material UI components.
- Utilization of CSS to customize MUI components.
- Utilization of GIT to version control.
- Utilization of Next.js.
- Utilization of TypeScript.
- Agile development.
- Remote worker.

FireFly.Bot

Full Stack Developer

October 2020 - May 2022 (1 year 8 months)

Curitiba, Paraná, Brazil

- Integration with CRM systems.
- Development of backend GraphQL queries and mutations.
- Database integration with Prisma ORM.
- CRUD development using React.
- Utilization of React Hooks with GraphQL queries and mutations.
- Performance improvements of Web pages by optimization of GraphQL queries.
- Development of chatbot conversation flows.
- Created Jest test cases.
- Utilization of TypeScript at both frontend and backend.
- Pagination and sorting on queries
- Importing and normalizing data from real estate databases
- Remote worker.

ACOM Sistemas

1 year 8 months

Web Developer

November 2019 - October 2020 (1 year)

Curitiba, Paraná, Brazil

- Creation and maintenance of SQLServer procedures and tables.
- Maintenance of CRM, ERP, SCM e CLM systems.
- Development of new screens and features for ERP, SCM and CLM systems using Javascript.
- Deployment of updates using tomcat for CRM, ERP, SCM and CLM.
- API documentation for SCM system.

Tester (Internship)

March 2019 - November 2019 (9 months)

Curitiba, Paraná, Brazil

- Unit tests, integration tests and functional tests.
- Procedures revision.

Procópio Industria e Comércio

Auxiliar de Produção

May 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 7 months)

Campo Largo, Paraná, Brasil

Education

Universidade Tuiuti do Paran ��

Postgraduate Degree, User Experience - UX · (October 2023 - April 2024)

Universidade Tuiuti do Paraná - UTP

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (February 2018 - December 2021)